He needed to trust her with his secret. She had to trust him with her life.
Shining Through is a drama, romance, thriller film directed by David Seltzer.
Spirited New Yorker Linda Voss goes to work for international lawyer and secret Office
of Strategic Services operative Ed Leland just before World War II.
As they fall in love, the United States enters the fight against Hitler, and
Linda volunteers to work for Ed spying undercover behind Nazi lines.
Assigned to uncover information about a German bomb, Linda also has personal motives to
fulfill: discovering the fate of her Jewish family members in Berlin.
Ed Leland, played by Michael Douglas.
Linda Voss, played by Melanie Griffith.
Franze-Otto Dietrich, played by Liam Neeson.
Margrete Von Eberstein, played by Joely Richardson.
Sunflower, played by John Gielgud.
Hedda Drescher, played by Hansi Jochmann.
Shining Through is a 1992 American World War II drama film written and directed
by David Seltzer and based on the 1988 novel by Susan Isaacs.
It stars Michael Douglas, Melanie Griffith, Liam Neeson, Joely Richardson, and John
Gielgud, and the original music score was composed by Michael Kamen.
The film was released in the United States on January 31, 1992.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book, nazi, germany, double agent.
The tone is emotional and intense.